https://www.bayviewtech.com.au/privacy-disclaimer

Now in stock
Belden’s REVConnect, the complete connectivity solution for CAT 5e, CAT 6 and CAT 6A UTP and STP – Call us today for more information and quote.
Privacy & Disclaimer
Bayview Technologies Pty Ltd is committed to providing meaningful privacy protection of visitors to our online sites. Accordingly, we have adopted this Privacy Statement to serve as the foundation for our privacy practices and procedures.
The Bayview Technologies Pty Ltd web site is structured so that you can visit without identifying yourself or revealing personal information.
In some circumstances, Bayview Technologies Pty Ltd may request personal information such as your name, e-mail address, company name or telephone number. Your response to these inquiries is strictly voluntary. Bayview Technologies Pty Ltd may use this information for statistical, demographic, marketing and/or transaction purposes, and to better understand the make-up of our customer base so we can improve our services consistent with our visitors’ interests. Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information which can identify you), be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with Bayview Technologies. If you do provide personal information, we will not disclose (share, sell or divulge) it to any external organisations in other than aggregated statistical form.
As a convenience to our visitors, Bayview Technologies Pty Ltd’s web site may contain links to a number of sites and PDF files not authored and/or owned by Bayview Technologies that we believe may offer useful information. Bayview Technologies is not responsible for any errors or technical performance data contained within these web sites and PDF files.
Melbourne
03 9462 4077
03 9462 4099
Sydney
0417 330 729
Brisbane
0417 764 268
Email Us
